Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertisements, 1932-1995
  - Procter & Gamble (See also Oversize boxes OV14-OV15)
    - Other products
      - Dawn dish detergent
        - 1975-1980, Consumer newspaper (Box 117)
      - Pert
        - 1953, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 117)
      - Pin-It
        - 1954, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 117)
      - Scope mouthwash
        - 1965-1980, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 117)
        - 1965-1979, Consumer newspaper (Box 117)
      - Secret deodorant
        - 1955, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 117)
      - Stardust
        - 1961-1967, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 118)
      - Velvet Skin lotion
        - 1944-1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 118)
      - Whirl vegetable shortening
        - 1957-1959, Consumer newspaper (Box 118)
      - White Naptha soap
        - 1945, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 118)
      - Wondra
        - 1977-1980, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 118)
  - Prudential Insurance Company of America (See also Oversize box OV15)
    - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 118)
    - 1939-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 118)
    - 1940, Consumer magazine (Box 118)
    - 1941, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1944, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1944-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 118)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1946-1947, Trade magazine (Box 118)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 118)
  - Railway Express Agency (See also Oversize box OV15)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box 119)
    - 1954-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 119)
    - 1954-1955, Trade magazine (Box 119)
    - 1954-1956, Trade newspaper (Box 119)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box 119)
    - 1955, Trade magazine (Box 119)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine (Box 119)
    - 1956, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 119)
    - 1957, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - 1957, Trade newspaper (Box 119)
    - 1958-1959, Consumer magazine (Box 119)
    - 1958, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - 1958-1960, Trade newspaper (Box 119)
    - 1959, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
    - 1960, Trade magazine (Box 120)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 120)
    - 1961-1962, Trade newspaper (Box 120)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Box 120)
  - S.C. Johnson (See also Oversize box OV15)
    - 1956-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
    - 1956-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box 120)
    - 1956-1964, Trade magazine (Box 120)
    - 1956-1957, Trade newspaper (Box 120)
    - 1958-1974, Consumer newspaper (Box 120)
    - 1961-1967, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
    - 1970-1978, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
  - Showtime/The Movie Channel (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1982, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
    - 1982-1983, Consumer newspaper (Box 120)
    - 1983, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - 1983, Trade magazine (Box 120)
    - 1984, Consumer magazine (Box 120)
  - Shulton (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
    - 1960-1967, Consumer newspaper (Box 121)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 121)
    - 1961, Trade newspaper (Box 121)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
    - 1963-1964, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
    - 1966-1967, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
  - Studebaker-Packard (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1955-1956, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
    - 1955-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 121)
    - 1955-1956, Trade magazine (Box 121)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine, 4 folders (Box 121)
    - 1956, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 121)
    - 1956-1957, Trade magazine (Box 121)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 121)
  - Texaco (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1961-1967, Consumer newspaper (Box 122)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1962, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1962-1963, Trade newspaper (Box 122)
    - 1963, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1963, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1964, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1964, Trade magazine (Box 122)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - 1966, Consumer magazine (Box 122)
    - 1966, Trade magazine (Box 122)
    - 1967, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1967-1968, Trade magazine (Box 123)
    - 1968, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - 1968, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - 1969, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1969-1970, Trade magazine (Box 123)
    - 1970-1971, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1970-1971, Consumer newspaper (Box 123)
    - 1971-1972, Consumer newspaper (Box 123)
    - 1971-1974, Trade magazine (Box 123)
    - 1972-1973, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1973, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1973-1977, Consumer newspaper (Box 123)
    - 1974, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1975, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1975-1980, Trade magazine (Box 123)
    - 1976-1977, Consumer magazine (Box 123)
    - 1977-1980, Consumer newspaper (Box 124)
    - 1978, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1979-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1980, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 124)
  - Warner-Lambert Pharmaceutical (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1939-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 124)
    - 1939-1941, Trade newspaper and magazine (Box 124)
    - 1940, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - 1941, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1942, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1970, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
  - West Point Pepperell (See also Oversize box OV17)
    - 1944, Consumer magazine (Box 124)
    - 1944, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - 1944, Trade magazine (Box 124)
    - 1944-1947, Trade newspaper (Box 125)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 125)
    - 1945-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 125)
    - 1945, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 125)
    - 1946, Trade magazine (Box 125)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - 1947-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 125)
    - 1947, Trade magazine (Box 125)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 125)
    - 1948, Trade magazine (Box 125)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box 125)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (Box 126)
    - 1949-1950, Trade newspaper (Box 126)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box 126)
    - 1950, Trade magazine (Box 126)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 126)
    - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 126)
    - 1951, Trade newspaper (Box 126)
    - 1952, Consumer magazine (Box 126)
    - 1952, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - 1952, Trade newspaper (Box 126)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Box 126)
    - 1953, Trade newspaper (Box 126)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box 126)
    - 1954-1955, Consumer newspaper (Box 126)
    - 1954, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - 1954-1956, Trade newspaper (Box 127)
    - 1955, Consumer newspaper (Box 127)
    - 1955, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - 1956-1957, Consumer magazine (Box 127)
    - 1956-1959, Consumer newspaper (Box 127)
    - 1956, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - 1956, Trade newspaper, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - 1957-1958, Trade magazine (Box 127)
    - 1957, Trade newspaper (Box 127)
    - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 127)
    - 1958, Trade newspaper (Box 128)
    - 1959-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 128)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1959, Trade newspaper (Box 128)
    - 1960, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1960-1966, Trade newspaper (Box 128)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - 1961-1968, Consumer newspaper (Box 128)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 128)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1963-1964, Consumer magazine (Box 128)
    - 1963-1964, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1965-1966, Consumer magazine (Box 128)
    - 1965-1966, Trade magazine (Box 128)
    - 1967-1968, Consumer magazine (Box 128)
  - Western Electric (See also Oversize box OV16)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - 1945-1947, Trade magazine (Box 129)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - 1946-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 129)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 129)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 1 of 4 folders (Box 129)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box 130)
    - 1948-1951, Trade magazine (Box 130)
    - 1949-1950, Consumer magazine (Box 130)
    - 1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 130)
    - 1950-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 130)
    - 1950-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 130)
    - 1950, Trade newspaper (Box 130)
    - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 130)
  - Western Union Telegraph Company
    - 1955-1957, Trade magazine (Box 131)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1956-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 131)
    - 1956-1960, Trade newspaper (Box 131)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1958-1959, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1959-1960, Trade magazine (Box 131)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 131)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1962-1963, Consumer magazine (Box 131)
    - 1962-1963, Trade magazine (Box 131)
  - Other Clients
    - Advertising Council (See also Oversize box OV1)
      - 1952-1954, 1961, Consumer newspaper (Box 132)
    - American Cancer Society
      - 1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 132)
    - American Pharmaceutical
      - 1965 (?), Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - American Safety Razor (ASR) (See also Oversize box OV1)
      - 1961-1965, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
      - 1961, 1964-1966, Consumer newspaper (Box 132)
      - 1961-1964, 1966, Trade magazine (includes television coverage chart) (Box 132)
      - 1964-1966, Consumer magazine (college publications) (Box 132)
    - AMK Corporation (United Fruit products) (See also Oversize box OV1)
      - 1970, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Anderson, Clayton and Company
      - 1979-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Angelique and Company
      - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Avis (See also Oversize box OV3)
      - 1969-1970, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
      - 1969-1972, Consumer newspaper (Box 132)
      - 1969-1972, Trade magazine (Box 132)
      - 1972-1973, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Banco de Brasil
      - 1979-1980, Trade magazine (Box 132)
      - 1980, Consumer magazine (includes travel/tourism) (Box 132)
    - Beck Shoe Store (See also Oversize box OV3)
      - 1970, Consumer newspaper (advertisements prepared by Jacqueline Brandwynne Association) (Box 132)
    - Beech-Nut (See also Oversize box OV3)
      - 1962-1964, Consumer magazine (baby food, cough drops) (Box 132)
      - 1963-1965, Consumer newspaper (Box 132)
      - 1963-1968, Trade magazine (Box 132)
      - 1965-1968, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Block Drug Company
      - 1972-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 132)
    - Bryton Chemical Company
      - 1958-1960, Trade magazine (Box 132)
    - Burlington Industries (Klopman Mills) (See also Oversize box OV4)
      - 1970-1971, Consumer magazine (uniforms) (Box 133)
      - 1970, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
      - 1970, Trade magazine (Box 133)
    - Caltex Petroleum Corporation (See also Oversize box OV4)
      - 1967-1970, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box 133)
      - 1971-1977, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box 133)
    - Canada Dry Corporation (See also Oversize box OV4)
      - 1967, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 133)
    - Champion International Corporation (See also Oversize box OV4)
      - 1972, 1974, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
      - 1973-1977, Consumer magazine (Box 133)
    - Cigar Institute of America (See also Oversize box OV5)
      - 1950-1951, Consumer magazine (targets college students) (Box 133)
      - 1950-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 133)
      - 1953-1955, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
      - 1954-1955, Consumer magazine (includes research) (Box 133)
    - Collier (?) (Bobby-MacBaby Chain)
      - 1971, Consumer magazine (Box 133)
    - Consolidated Food Corporation (See also Oversize box OV5)
      - 1974-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 133)
      - 1974-1977, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
      - 1974-1978, Consumer newspaper (Box 133)
    - Continental Airlines (See also Oversize box OV5)
      - 1974, Consumer magazine (Box 133)
    - Crum and Forster (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1972-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
      - 1972-1980, Trade magazine (Box 134)
      - 1975-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1980, Trade magazine (Box 134)
    - Drake Bakeries (Drake's Cakes)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
      - 1935-1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
    - Dr. Pepper Company (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1941, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
      - 1941-1942, Consumer magazine (wartime advertising) (Box 134)
      - 1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
      - 1941-1942, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
      - 1941, Trade magazine (Box 134)
    - Drug Development Corporation (Cough-Ex)
      - 1971, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
    - Eastern Airlines
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
    - Ed Dalton (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1964-1965, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
      - 1964, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
    - Emery Worldwide
      - 1983, Consumer magazine (Box 134)
    - Endeavor Publishing Corporation (Win magazine)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 134)
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1962-1968, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 135)
      - 1963-1968, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 135)
      - 1963, Trade magazine (Vigran, Sweeta) (Box 135)
      - 1964, Consumer newspaper (Vigran, Sweeta) (Box 135)
    - Fitgers Brewing Company (Fitzger's beer) (See also Oversize box OV7)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - Galloping Gourmet
      - 1973, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - Gillette (See also Oversize box OV11)
      - 1970, Consumer magazine (Tracc II) (Box 135)
      - 1970-1972, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 135)
      - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (disposable razors) (Box 135)
      - 1976-1980, Consumer newspaper (disposable razors) (Box 135)
    - G. Kreuger Brewing (beer and ale)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
      - 1948-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
      - 1948-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - GMF Robotics: See also Oversize box OV11 (Box 135)
    - Greater New York Fund
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - Grove Laboratories (Bromo Quinine)
      - 1955-1957, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
      - 1955-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - Hanes Corporation (L'Erin cosmetics) (See also Oversize box OV11)
      - 1979-1981, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - Hasbro Industries (See also Oversize box OV11)
      - 1969-1977, Consumer newspaper and magazine (multiple products) (Box 135)
    - Hunt Foods and Industries
      - 1968, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - Hy-Gain Electronics (CB radio) (See also Oversize box OV11)
      - 1977, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - Indonesia (Republic of)
      - 1969, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - Interbank Card Association (Signet bank card)
      - 1977 (?), Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - International Silver Company (Rogers silverplate)
      - 1934-1935, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
    - J.C. Eno (United States) Limited
      - 1936-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 135)
      - 1937-1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 135)
    - J.H. Westerbeke Corporation
      - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 135)
    - Kane Miller Corporation (Sunnyland)
      - 1981-1983, Consumer magazine (Superman brand peanut butter, raisins) (Box 135)
    - Lenox China (See also Oversize box OV12)
      - 1948-1950, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1948-1953, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 136)
      - 1948-1954, Trade magazine (Box 136)
      - 1951-1952, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
    - Liggett and Myers Tobacco Company
      - 1982, Consumer magazine (Red Man chewing tobacco) (Box 136)
    - Lorillard Corporation (Kent) (See also Oversize box OV12)
      - 1969, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1969, Consumer newspaper (Box 136)
    - Marine Midland Bank (See also Oversize box OV12)
      - 1976, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1976, Consumer newspaper (Box 136)
      - 1976-1980, Trade magazine (Box 136)
      - 1980, Consumer magazine (some international advertisements) (Box 136)
      - 1980, Trade newspaper (some international advertisements) (Box 136)
    - MCI Communications
      - 1987, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
    - McKesson and Robbins (See also Oversize box OV12)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1944-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box 136)
      - 1947-1949, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
    - Milliken and Company (Visa fabrics)
      - 1979-1980, Trade magazine (Box 136)
      - 1979, Trade magazine (Box 136)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association (See also Oversize box OV12)
      - 1973-19794, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1977, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1977, Trade magazine (Box 136)
    - National Association of Manufacturers (See also Oversize box OV13)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 136)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 136)
      - 1948, Trade magazine (Box 136)
    - New York World's Fair (See also Oversize box OV13)
      - 1964, Trade magazine (Box 137)
    - New York State Citizen's Council on Traffic Safety
      - 1962, Booklets (Box 137)
    - Old Hickory (Diplomat)
      - 1947, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 137)
      - 1947, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 137)
    - Parker Pen Company (See also Oversize box OV13)
      - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
    - P. Ballantine and Sons (See also Oversize box OV13)
      - 1933-1935, Consumer and trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 137)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (beer and ale) (Box 137)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (beer and ale) (Box 137)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (beer and ale) (Box 137)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper (beer and ale) (Box 137)
    - Peter Eckrich and Sons Incorporated
      - 1976-1977, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
      - 1978-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
    - Peter Paul Incorporated (See also Oversize box OV13)
      - 1970, 1972, Consumer and trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 137)
      - 1970, Consumer newspaper (Box 137)
    - Pitney Bowes: See Oversize box OV13 (Box 137)
    - Quaker Oats Company
      - 1938-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
    - Revlon Incorporated
      - 1971, Consumer magazine (advertisements prepared by Jacqueline Brandwynne Association) (Box 137)
    - Richardson-Vick (See also Oversize box OV15)
      - 1966-1973, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 137)
      - 1966-1979, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box 137)
      - 1966-1970, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 137)
      - 1973-1980, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 137)
    - Sauce n'Serve
      - 1974, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
    - Savings Bank Association of the State of New York (See also Oversize box OV15)
      - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
      - 1959-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 137)
      - 1960, 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
      - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box 137)
    - Schenley Ind. Incorporated (See also Oversize box OV15)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Three Feathers) (Box 137)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Old Stagg, Three Feathers) (Box 137)
      - 1948-1951, Consumer newspaper (Old Stagg, Three Feathers) (Box 137)
      - 1948-1951, Trade magazine (Old Stagg, Three Feathers) (Box 137)
    - Schick (See also Oversize box OV15)
      - 1957-1958, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 138)
      - 1958-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box 138)
      - 1958-1960, Trade magazine (some international advertisements) (Box 138)
      - 1959-1961, Consumer newspaper (some international advertisements) (Box 138)
    - Schlitz (See also Oversize box OV15)
      - 1979-1980, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 138)
      - 1980, Consumer newspaper (Tribute light beer) (Box 138)
    - Securities Industries Association
      - 1973-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 138)
    - Standard Brands (Planters products)
      - 1976-1978, Consumer newspaper (Box 138)
      - 1977-1979, Consumer magazine (Box 138)
    - Sterling Drug Company (Glenbrook Labs)
      - 1965-1970, Consumer magazine (Vanquish) (Box 138)
    - Sun Oil Company
      - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 138)
    - This Week Magazine (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1954-1956, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
      - 1954, Trade magazine (Box 139)
      - 1954-1957, Trade newspaper (Box 139)
      - 1955, Trade magazine (Box 139)
      - 1956, Trade magazine (Box 139)
      - 1957, Trade magazine (Box 139)
    - Time Incorporated (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1973-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
    - UNICEF (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1971-1973, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
      - 1972-1974, Trade magazine (Box 139)
      - 1974-1979, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
    - Unicom Group of Insurance Company (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1973, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
    - United Fund of Westchester (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - Undated, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
    - United States Rubber Company (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1964-1967, Consumer magazine (Royal golf equipment) (Box 139)
      - 1966-1967, Consumer and trade newspaper (multiple products) (Box 139)
      - 1966, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 139)
      - 1966, Trade magazine (Naugahyde) (Box 139)
      - 1966, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 139)
    - United States Treasury Department (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1983, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
    - Upholstery Leather Group Incorporated (See also Oversize box OV16)
      - 1957, Trade magazine (Box 139)
    - West End Brewery Company (Utica Club beer)
      - 1965-1966, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
      - 1965-1966, Consumer newspaper (Box 139)
    - Winthrop and Ward (Froth Dry Cleaner)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 139)
    - Yardley of London (See also Oversize box OV17)
      - 1968-1969, Consumer magazine (some advertisements targeted at men) (Box 139)
      - 1970, Consumer and trade magazine (some advertisements targeted at African American women) (Box 139)
      - 1971, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
      - 1972, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
      - 1972-1973, Consumer magazine (Box 139)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Advertising Council
      - 1952, USO (Box OV1)
      - 1962-1963, Better Schools, 2 folders (Box OV1)
    - Allied Chemical
      - 1959-1960, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1960, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1960-1963, Trade newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1961, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1961-1962, Trade newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1961-1965, Consumer magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1962, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1963, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1963-1970, Trade newspaper (Box OV1)
      - 1964, Trade magazine (Box OV1)
      - 1964-1965, Trade magazine (Box OV1)